CONTACT ME AT

• Abuja, Nigeria



patienceadajah@gmail.com



in https://linkedin.com/in/patience-adajah

SKILLS SUMMARY

HTML CSS Apollo GraphQL Next.js

Debugging Git RestApi React

JavaScript Version Control BootStrap

Critical Thinking Collaboration Negotiation

Search Engine Optimization (SEO)

Creative Problem Solving

PROJECTS

pro.motionwares.com

I built the front-end of the web platform (pro.motionwares.com) using HTML, CSS, JavaScript and React. The project is basically a dashboard to get the profiles of digital professionals.

https://cbtpal.com

This project is a platform to create Computer Based Test(CBT). Users of the platform which are mostly people in the education sector, can create and manage assessments for their students on the platform. I worked as the front-end developer implementing designs to code.

INTEREST

Reading

Patience Adajah

Front-end Software Developer

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a result oriented software engineer with years of experience with front-end technologies. I have a knack for building and optimizing interactive user-friendly and feature rich websites. I pay strong attention to details to deliver efficient web solutions. Over the years, I have worked with HTML, CSS, BootStrap, JavaScript, React and NextJs.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer

Motionwares Digital Solutions (Abuja) | November, 2019 - Present

- I worked as a front-end engineer, implementing designs to code
- Built projects that were responsive across screens of different sizes and compatible across web browsers.

Intern Software Developer

Yatice Digital Solutions (Ibadan, Oyo State) | May 2019 - September, 2019

- Developed the backend of an ASP.NET MVC application (examtone.com) using the C# language.
- Designed and developed the database for a project using MS SQL server.
- Performed API testing and documented the results.
- Remedied bug reports and handled other user issues.

International Development Intern

Dataville Research LLC (Remote) | January 2019 - April 2019

- Gained hands-on experience with mobile data collection and analysis using Open Data Kit (ODK).
- Developed request for proposal (RFP) documents for donorfunded projects.
- Collected and analyzed data for better decision making with data analysis software (Microsoft Excel and SPSS).

VOLUNTEERING EXPERIENCE

Communications Manager at Global Entrepreneur Leaders Academy (GELA)

June 2018 - July 2019

EDUCATION

University of Benin

B.Sc Animal and Environmental Biology | 2013 - 2017